Siobhan Powell

Junior Quality Assurance Engineer and Department Lead with 7 years of startup experience, generating end-to-end manual and automated testing strategies from scratch, as well as overseeing the development and integration of company-wide quality assurance protocols.

Omaha, NE (402) 889-0819 mail@siobhan.zip



EXPERIENCE

Rush ReCommerce, Omaha NE — Junior Quality Assurance Engineer

September 2022 - PRESENT

- Managed QA sprint planning based on test case generation and automation priorities, allowing for rapid story processing while maintaining extant test suites.
- Developed testing strategies within partnered tools, such as Shopify, LogicBroker, as well as direct API unit & end-to-end testing.
- Established User Acceptance Testing protocol, including generating training material and scheduling demonstrations both virtually and in-person of new and updated feature releases.
- Provided critical feedback for requirements gathering sessions and fielded communication with end-users for bug tracking and follow-on development.
- Documented research on Rush ReCommerce SDLC and frameworks for automation testing for investment presentation.

Rush ReCommerce, Omaha NE — *Manual Quality Assurance Analyst*

August 2019 - September 2022

- Implemented and managed manual test casing procedures
- Created and maintained manual test case documentation for both backend product processing and customer-facing test scenarios.
- Managed multiple varied testing environments and generated test data collections as needed.
- Established hardware and software testing acceptance criteria,
 and assisted in establishing a consistent company wide IT
 hardware management scheme for training and quality purposes.

The Rush Market, Omaha NE — Warehouse Coordinator

May 2017 - August 2019

- Established integral returns process for partnered vendors, resulting in a new contract type, greatly expanding possible vendor relationships and revenue possibilities.
- Developed and utilized Material Warehouse Managerial systems to ascertain catalog number, size, color, and quantity of merchandise currently stored, and determine pick rate based on category sale data.
- Maintained and updated all records/logs relative to shipping and receiving

SKILLS

Experience with:

- -JavaScript
- -MySQL
- -Postman
- -GIT
- -JIRA
- -Cypress
- -Nightwatch.js

API Testing, Black-Box Testing, Regression Testing

Agile Methodologies, Kanban, Sprint Planning, Feature Driven Development

User Acceptance Testing, Training Documentation Maintenance, User Feedback Collection & Tracking

AWARDS

_

-

LANGUAGES

English

EDUCATION

University of Nebraska-Lincoln, Lincoln NE — Partial Undergrad

August 2015 - June 2016

PROJECTS -

Corporate Intranet —

Facilitated the establishment of an corporate intranet service for Rush ReCommerce. Using a combination of available Atlassian, G-Suite, and Corelink services, I was able to develop an Employee Newsletter, working Knowledge Base, Employee Directory and Department Hierarchy Tree, among other items to be used by the collective staff in a central, internally hosted tool.

Helpdesk Portal & Standard Operating Procedure —

As part of the intranet service, I also facilitated the first Help Desk Portal for the Rush Market, comprised of a self-guided directory for a User to classify the nature of request, submission and ticketing tools, ticket management and SLA structure, as well as a knowledge base for D.I.Y troubleshooting.

This also included establishment of Standard Operating Procedure, setting the expectations of service for Help Desk Operators and Help Desk Users.